Hashem Al-Saqqa



hashem.b.saqqa@gmail.com



+972592989725



linkedin.com/in/hashem-saqqa

Summary

I Have 4+ years of experience as an Android Native (Java and Kotlin) Developer. Mobile app guidelines and realize that UX/UI quality is one of the essential things in mobile apps. I always deliver pixel-perfect layouts tested on various devices, possess strong analytical and problem-solving skills, efficiently manage projects while keeping up-to-date with the latest development trends, techniques, and technologies.

Experience



Technical Trainer

UNRWA

Apr 2022 - Aug 2022 (5 months)

Teacher Assistance in computer engineering

University College of Applied Sciences, Gaza, Palestine Feb 2022 - Present (1 year 5 months)

Android Developer

Freelancer

Apr 2019 - Present (4 years 3 months)

Education



Islamic University of Gaza

Master of Data Science



Islamic University of Gaza

Bachelor of Computer Science

Skills

Android Java/Kotlin • RxJava • Firebase • REST APIs • Model-view-viewmodel (MVVM) • Android Jetpack • GitHub • Dagger | Hilt • Room Da • Google Maps API